http://www.electricreliability.org/privacy-policy

Home
What is ERCC?
is the owner of this web site. We
are committed to the responsible management of consumer information, and
Internet user privacy is a high priority.
On electricreliability.org we will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you
(such as name, address, telephone number or email address) unless you
send it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personal information
collected, please do not submit it on our site.
If you submit your email online you may receive periodic mailings
from us with information on events within the company about research
developments, new employees, acquisitions and the like. Each mailing
will contain instructions on how you can remove your name from our
mailing list.
We further promise not to sell, loan, rent, give or barter any part of your personal information to any person or entity which is not part of The Electric Reliability Coordinating Council.
If you have already submitted your information and would like us to remove it from our files, please contact us at info@electricreliability.org.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information is Collected Automatically
When anyone visits this web site, our server automatically recognizes
the type of Internet browser and computer operating system they use and
the domain name of the Web site from which they arrived at the site.
This non-personally identifiable information is collected automatically
and used for internal review only.
Please e-mail questions or requests for more information about our privacy policies to info@electricreliability.org.
©  2012 – 2020 ERCC Electric Reliability Coordinating Council
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
Site Map
